Summer in the City is a romance, comedy, tv movie film directed by Vic Sarin.
When a small town woman with southern charm is given a big promotion managing a store in the Big
Apple, she tries to adopt a big city personality and it leads to disastrous results.
Taylor, played by Julianna Guill.
Phillip, played by Marc Bendavid.
Alyssa, played by Vivica A. Fox.
Mindy, played by Marla Sokoloff.
Kendall, played by Natasha Henstridge.
Courtney, played by Christie Burke.
2016 in film is an overview of events, including the highest-grossing films, award
ceremonies, festivals, a list of films released, and notable deaths.
The film explores themes of fashion, manhattan, new york city, clothing store.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.